Finding Aid for Michigan. Justice of the Peace (Ypsilanti: Township) records, 1874-1910
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan. Justice of the Peace (Ypsilanti: Township) records 1874-1910
Michigan. Justice of the Peace (Ypsilanti: Township)
22 oversize volumes
86322 CC Outsize
Justice, civil and criminal docket books of the first and second districts of Ypsilanti township, Washtenaw County, Michigan.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The provenance of the record group is unknown.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The justice of the peace for Ypsilanti township in Washtenaw County, Michigan was responsible for hearing and deciding cases, both civil and criminal.
The docket books are arranged by district and then by category: justice, civil, and criminal.
Subjects:
Courts.; Justices of the peace--Michigan--Ypsilanti (Township); Washtenaw County (Mich.); Ypsilanti (Mich.: Township); Michigan. Justice of the Peace (Ypsilanti: Township)
- First District
  - Justice Docket book John G. Crane, presiding, May 1874-May 1877 (Volume 1)
    (volume no. 1)
  - Justice Docket book, John G. Crane and P.M. Skinner, presiding, May 1877-August 1879 (Volume 2)
    (volume no. 2)
  - Justice Docket book P.M. Skinner and D.C. Griffin, presiding, August 1879-March 1887 (Volume 3)
    (volume no. 3)
  - Civil Docket book, D.C. Griffin & F.P. Bogardiis, presiding, March 1887-January 1892 (Volume 4)
    (volume no. 4)
  - Civil Docket book, F.P. Bogardus, presiding, January 1892-July 1894 (Volume 5)
    (volume no. 5)
  - Civil Docket book, Herbert W. Childs, presiding, July 1894-January 1897 (Volume 6)
    (volume no. 6)
  - Civil Docket book, Herbert W. Childs, presiding, January 1897-July 1902 (Volume 7)
    (volume no. 7)
  - Civil Docket book, Herbert W. Childs and William S. Putnam, presiding, July 1902-June 1906 (Volume 8)
    (volume no. 8)
  - Civil Docket book, William S. Putnam & George R. Gunn, presiding, June 1906-July 1909 (Volume 9)
    (volume no. 9)
  - Criminal Docket book, D.C. Griffin & F.P. Bogardus, presiding, January 1886-December 1891 (Volume 14)
    (volume no. 14)
  - Criminal Docket book, F.P. Bogardus, presiding, January 1892-January 1894 (Volume 15)
    (volume no. 15)
  - Criminal Docket book, Herbert W. Childs, presiding, July 1894-December 1897 (Volume 16)
    (volume no. 16)
  - Criminal Docket book, Herbert W. Childs, presiding, January 1898-March 1900 (Volume 17)
    (volume no. 17)
  - Criminal Docket book, Herbert W. Childs and William S. Putnam, presiding, February 1902-June 1905 (Volume 18)
    (volume no. 18)
  - Criminal Docket book, William. S. Putnam and George R. Gunn, presiding, July 1905-June 1910 (Volume 19)
    (volume no. 19)
- Second District
  - Justice Docket book, James M. Forsyth and Frank Joslyn, presiding, May 1878-April 1887 (Volume 10)
    (volume no. 10)
  - Civil Docket Book, Frank Joslyn and Walter P. Beach, presiding, April 1887-December 1895 (Volume 11)
    (volume no. 11)
  - Civil Docket Book, Walter P. Beach and Frank Joslyn, presiding, October 1895-January 1905 (Volume 12)
    (volume no.12 )
  - Civil Docket Book, Frank Joslyn & George R. Gunn, presiding, January 1905-June 1910 (Volume 13)
    (volume no. 13)
  - Criminal Docket book, Frank Joslyn, presiding, September 1901-February 1904 (Volume 20)
    (volume no. 20)
  - Criminal Docket book, Frank Joslyn, presiding, March 1904-November 1905 (Volume 21)
    (volume no. 21)
  - Criminal Docket book, Frank Joslyn and George R. Gunn, presiding, November 1905-June 1908 (Volume 22)
    (volume no. 22)